# **Andrea Moulding**

**Full Stack Software Developer** 

808.781.5475

ANDREA.MOULDING@GMAIL.COM

LINKEDIN.COM/IN/AMOULDING GITHUB.COM/ANDREAMSOFCAKE

#### **PROFILE**

Dynamic Full Stack Software Developer experienced in building rich interfaces and internet applications.

#### SKILLS

- Javascript: NodeJS, ReactJS, Flux, Javascript: NodeJS, ReactJS, Flux,

  KeystoneJS, EmberJS, jQuery, D3JS,

  Angular IS

  CSS3, Bootstrap, SASS

  PostgreSQL, MongoDB

  Python 3, Diaggo AngularJS
- HTML5, Handelbars

- CSS3, Bootstrap, SASS
- · Python 3, Django
- PHP, Drupal

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## List Media Inc. - Dec 2015 to current - Contract Full Stack Developer

Interactive web app using EmberJS and ExpressJS frameworks. Developed a real time WSYWIG editor for email templates. Designed user experience when working with template system. Styled app with CSS pre-processing, SASS.

### SDK Core Corporation - Nov 2015 to Jul 2016 - Contract Full Stack Developer

Utilized Flux architecture to create client administration, inventory and user management portal. Utilized ReactJS architecture to create UI/UX for user on touch screen proprietary kiosk. Created responsive components with ReactJS for realtime updates to the UI.

#### American Green - May 2015 to October 2015 - Front End Developer

Utilized KeystoneJS and ReactJS to create multi user administration and social network. Implemented responsive components with ReactJS on social network site. Used Webpack module bundler to manage build process. Produced vendor dashboard for purchases and inventory management. Contributed to user management and identification verification of users.

## **EDUCATION**

## Portland Code School,

Full stack Immersion - June 2014 to November 2014

## Portland Community College,

Project Management - 2013

#### University of Utah,

Theater Design, BFA 2004